Muhamad Rizal Gustian Aryanto

085817206901 · rizalgustian28813@gmail.com · @rzalgustn_ Jakarta, Indonesia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhamadrizalgustian/ https://bit.ly/rizalportofolio2024

I am interested in digital media, passionate about creating something unique, modern, and functional in the graphic design and graphic arts industry for more than 3 years as a graphic design, digital marketing, communication and event planner.

My creativity in my work has made a positive impact on various projects and clients that I have handled.

Professional Experiences

Social Media Specialist, Graphic Design, Video Editor, Content Creation, Digital Marketing PT. Menara Golden Travel

- Create engaging visual content for posts, stories, and posters, be it moving videos or promotional videos and manage social media accounts by planning, scheduling, posting relevant content, and interacting with followers to build strong communication.
- successfully reached over 144k unfollowed instagram accounts within one month.

Team Media Creative | Freelance

H. Hasan Basri Umar (Komisi 3 DPRD DKI Fraksi Nasdem)

- Rensponsible for make design H. Hasan Basri Umar for political campaign.
- Make plans and concepts from briefs converted into visual form. Visual planning, along with copywriting in a layout

Freelance Graphic Designer

- Rensponsible for make design by brief from client
- Generated concepts and followed through to production. Design everything from program logos, merch, posters, special project and more

Digital Marketing Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

PT. Sahid Gema Wisata (Sahid Group)

- Provide branding materials in the form of designs for campaigns develop
- Implement digital marketing strategies to increase visibility and sales of Hajj and Umrah packages
- Responsible for the overall visual aspects of advertising or media campaigns.

Organization Experiences

Head of Administration and Secretariat of the Islamic Student Association Faculty of Da'wa and Communication Science

2024 - Present

Faculty of Da'wa and Communication Science

- Manage and develop the website and learning management system as well as activate the organization's social media packed with content, feeds, flyers etc.
- Implementation of a good administrative system and organizing document management.

Member of youth ranggers indonesia

2022- Present

· Participate in seminars, training and active in self-development activities

Student Senate of the Faculty of Da'wah and Communication Sciences

2024

Chairman of Commission 1 on Law and Legislation

- Become a student representative, convey student aspirations, improve discipline, support the success of the tri dharma program of higher education.
- Fostering student behavior in accordance with the norms that apply in the campus environment.

- Document and archive meeting minutes and key organization files
- · Handle internal and external comunnications, crafting and sending official messages
- Organize and coordinate meetings, events, and activities including logistical support and maintain social media and website, ensuring up to date information

Deputy arts and skills section ISMI Daar El-Qolam

2019 - 2020

• Plan and execute art activities, such as performances, art exhibitions, etc.

Education

UIN Syarif Hidayatullah

Jakarta

Faculty of Da'wa and Communication Science

2020 - 2024

Da'wah Management, IPK 3,59 (Cum Laude)

Daar El Qolam Islamic Boarding School

Tangerang, Banten

Social Science

2018 - 2020

Skills and Rewards

Software Skill: Photoshoop, Ilustraor, Canva, PicsArt, Capcut. Microsoft Office

Soft Skill: Creative, Communication, Team Work, Adaptability, Organizational, Critical Thinking

Rewards: BAZNAS RI Jakarta Future Scholarship (2023, 2024), Kind English Course TOEFL (525) Score